AVIKUMAR LUBDHI

Pune, India · (+91)-83294-38234 · ravikumar.lubdhi@gmail.com · LinkedIn · Portfolio

SUMMARY

OA Automation Engineer with 1+ years of experience and strong working knowledge of the agile development life cycle in the ERP domain. Proven ability to write and implement test cases, test scripts, and tools that improve the quality of software products.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Mapsoft Solutions, Pune, IN

Mar 2022 - Present

QA Automation Engineer

- Designed, wrote, and implemented system-wide high-level scenarios, test cases, test scripts and weekly status reports.
- Developed ~40 automated test scripts using core Java with the help of Selenium WebDriver.
- Performed load and stress testing using JMeter.
- Performed smoke and regression testing on a web application.
- Reported bugs to the development team in an agile workflow and efficiently assisted with root cause analysis in bug resolution.

Environment: Selenium WebDriver, Java, MySQL, Jenkins, TestNG, Maven, JMeter, JIRA, Xray, Microsoft Excel, Eclipse, Git, Bitbucket, Windows.

INTERNSHIP

ArkinIndia Software Solutions, Sangli, IN

Apr 2021 – Jun 2021

Web Designer Intern

- Developed and designed intuitive and user-centric user interfaces using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
- Worked with front-end web developers to deploy designs using Figma.
- Collaborated closely with the company to identify customer needs and demands.

EDUCATION

Annasaheb Dange College Of Engineering & Technology, Ashta

Jun 2021

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science & Engineering

• CPI: 7.13

Jath Highschool & Junior College of Arts & Science, Jath **Higher Secondary, Science**

Mar 2016

Percentage: 58.48%

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Programming Languages: Java, Python, C++, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, SQL

Testing Skills: Selenium WebDriver, TestNG, JUnit, PyTest, Robot, Mayen, Jenkins, Jmeter, Postman, Xray, Tableau Desktop, Jupyter Notebook, Software Testing Life Cycle (STLC), Defect Life Cycle.

Bug Tracking Tools: Jira, Microsoft Excel

Databases: Microsoft SQL Server, MySQL

Soft Skills: Quick Learner, Critical Thinking, Detail-Oriented, Curious, Kind.

CERTIFICATIONS

- MasterClass Software Testing with Jira & Agile Be a QA Lead
- Selenium WebDriver with Java Basics to Advanced + Frameworks
- JMETER from Scratch on Live Apps -Performance Testing
- Tableau Fundamental
- SQL for Data Analysis
- Python Basics for Data Science
- **Building Containerized Applications on AWS**

PROJECTS

Doc-Tient Online Consultation

Jan 2020 - Jun 2021

- Doc-Tient is a web application for online appointment booking and consultation through video conference.
- The doc-Tient system improves doctors' work and allows patients to book appointments simply and effectively.

Movie Recommendation System

Jul 2019 - Nov 2019

- Aggregated data from IMDB and used K-Nearest-Neighbors in Scikit-learn to build a better movie recommendation system.
- Built visualizations in Python (Matplotlib, Pandas) to show the best movies based on ratings.

CO-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- Attended the Tableau Conference 2021 (Virtual).
- Attended the International Pycon India Conference (2019).
- Steering committee member of Discovery 2K19 at ADCET.
- Participated in an Open Data Science workshop conducted by Techfest, IIT Bombay (2018).
- Participated in a Python workshop organized by WLUG, Sangli (2018).
- Worked as the coordinator for the Discovery 2K17 National Level Technical Symposium.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Date Of Birth - 30th March 1998

Nationality - Indian Gender - Male

Languages - English, Hindi, Marathi, Kannada.Interests - Watching Movies, Reading, Travelling.

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that to the best of my knowledge and belief, the information mentioned above is authentic.

Date:

Place: Pune Ravikumar Lubdh